<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>howto on True web artisans</title>
    <link>https://truewebartisans.com/tags/howto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in howto on True web artisans</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC-ND 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 20:10:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://truewebartisans.com/tags/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make git clone for my private repository on GitHub?</title>
      <link>https://truewebartisans.com/posts/2019/09/how-to-git-clone-private-repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 20:10:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truewebartisans.com/posts/2019/09/how-to-git-clone-private-repository/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome! This is another article in the “How to” series.
This time, we will try to do without magic!
Objectives of the article  Show one of the easiest ways to clone your private GitHub repository; Train your console skills;  Let&amp;rsquo;s clone it! First, generate SSH key on your VDS:
sudo ssh-keygen  Choose any name if you want, I use default name of key: rsa_key.
 Next step, create SSH config:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a native macOS app on Golang and React.js with full code protection (without magic)</title>
      <link>https://truewebartisans.com/posts/2019/05/native-macos-app-on-golang-and-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 23:10:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truewebartisans.com/posts/2019/05/native-macos-app-on-golang-and-react/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the next article in the “How to” series! This time, we will analyze the creation of a native desktop application for macOS, write a little code on Golang and React.js, which will have copy protection.
This time, we will try to do without magic!
Objectives of the article  Show one of the easiest ways to create a native desktop application for macOS on Golang; Show the option to protect the code of your application from being modified by third parties (for example, during commercial distribution);  Instruments Work Environment  Go 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>